Thomas Lepper

756 Shaker Road Longmeadow, MA 01106 (413) 565-5262 tomlepper@comcast.net http://www.linkedin.com/in/53lep

Professional Profile

Technically sophisticated and business-savvy management professional with a pioneering career reflecting strong leadership qualifications coupled with "hands-on" IT expertise. In past 4 years, delivered \$300,000 through system and process improvements. Superior track record of delivering simultaneous mission critical projects, on time and under budget.

"Tom has extensive knowledge in providing Internet and technology solutions to the commercial and publishing sectors. He is very client focused and honest, consistently finding creative, strategic, and cost-effective solutions to help support the business units he supports. He has provided strong executive leadership at Disney, is a mentor to his colleagues, and is a significant force behind the company's success." July 7, 2011, Jim Awiszus, Northeastern Regional Account Manager, Quark (business partner)

Strengths & Accomplishments

- ▶ Project Management Team Building & Leadership
 - "Received "Spot Bonus" from DPW President, for role as Project Lead in Data Center build-out
 - Nominated by peers for the Peer-to-Peer Award
- ► Process Improvement
 - Championed the upgrade of all network hardware and phones to increase file transfer and productivity
 - Redesigned the hierarchy automated asset workflow for editorial, creative and production departments
 - Manage and execute the archival all final digital assets to online database for repurpose
- ► Customer Service and Support
 - Provided customer service and technical support of magazine production processes
 - Developed and created internal web site for informational, support procedures
 - Manage Data Center physical environment and daily backups
- ► Call Center Management
 - 1st & 2nd level VOIP support for Cisco Call Manager and Cisco Unity Voice Mail Servers
- ► Service Delivery Systems
 - Negotiated software and hardware providers service contracts delivering 300,000 in savings
 - Administered QPS Publishing System to create print, and mobile formats in a production environment
 - Manage the delivery of multiple, simultaneous software with the introduction of new technologies

Professional History

WALT DISNEY CO., Disney Publishing Worldwide

IT Business Systems Analyst - 2004-2011

Deliver and direct all IT Services supporting the satellite editorial office for Disney's FamilyFun Magazine. Oversee the Service Center Help Desk ticketing system by managing local outsourced staff supporting the desktop population.

WALT DISNEY CO., Disney Publishing Worldwide

Production Technology Associate - 2000-2004

Provide Technical Services for FamilyFun, Disney Magazine. Manage editorial trafficking, color proofing from creative through prepress and the execution of color mark-up, of monthly Magazines.

ADVO Systems Inc.

Macintosh Technician/Graphic Designer - 1996-2000

Administered support and service for all hardware, software, local servers and printers. Conducted preflight and trouble-shooting prepress files. Design and create direct mail marketed advertisements.

ALVIN & Co.

Print Buyer/Production Coordinator - 1995-1996

Negotiation and purchase of all printed material. Coordinated mail requirements for first, third and fourth class promotional product. Review all desktop files, separations, blue-lines, photography, press approvals.

Education

Montserrat College of Art, Beverly, MA Fine Art: Lithography/Printmaking/Painting/Design

Technical Skills

Operating Systems: Windows 98, Windows Professional, Windows XP,

Macintosh OSX Leopard, Snow Leopard, Lion

Software: Microsoft Office 2004, 2008, 2011, Project, Visio, Adobe CS3, CS4, CS5, Quark Xpress, Copy Desk, Quark Publishing System, QPS Web Hub, Quark QLA, Apple Remote Desktop, Apple Server Admin, Bru Server Admin, Deploy Studio, SAP, Vital QIP, FileMaker Pro, FileMaker Server, Cisco Call Manager, Cisco Unity, Universal Type Server, Suitcase Fusion, Citrix Client, Terminal, WebEx.

Professional Development

Adobe Digital Services Training, Building a Digital Magazine, Adobe Inc.

Unix Command Line Basics for System Monitoring and Control, Core Solutions Inc.

ElementK, Cisco Advanced Technology, Online Training

Adobe CS3, CS4 Training, Core Solutions Inc.

Quark QPS Administrator Training, Quark Inc.

Quark QPS Manager Training Quark Inc.

SAP Casual Buyer Training